Two worlds collide. One survives.
Transformers: The Last Knight is a action, adventure,
science fiction film directed by Michael Bay.
Humans and Transformers are at war.
Optimus Prime is gone.
The key to saving our future lies buried in the secrets of the
past, in the hidden history of Transformers on Earth.
Saving our world falls upon the shoulders of an unlikely alliance: Cade
Yeager; Bumblebee; an English Lord; and an Oxford Professor.
Cade Yeager, played by Mark Wahlberg.
Viviane Wembly, played by Laura Haddock.
Optimus Prime (voice), played by Peter Cullen.
Sir Edmund Burton, played by Anthony Hopkins.
Bumblebee (voice), played by Erik Aadahl.
Colonel William Lennox, played by Josh Duhamel.
Transformers: The Last Knight is a 2017 American science fiction
action film based on Hasbro's Transformers toy line.
It is the fifth in the Transformers film series.
The film was directed by Michael Bay and written by Art
Marcum, Matt Holloway, and Ken Nolan.
It stars Mark Wahlberg reprising his role from Age of Extinction, while
Josh Duhamel reprises his role from the first three films.
Stanley Tucci returns as a different character after also appearing in
Age of Extinction, with Anthony Hopkins joining the cast.
In the film, inventor Cade Yeager is gifted a Talisman by a dying Transformer knight, and is soon recruited by an
eccentric British professor to save the world from the impending threat of a Cybetronian Sorceress.
Transformers: The Last Knight premiered on June 18, 2017, at the Odeon Luxe Leicester Square in
London and was released in the United States on June 21, by Paramount Pictures.
The film received generally negative reviews from critics, and grossed $605 million against a production budget
between $217–260 million and losing Paramount an estimated $100 million on the theatrical release.
It was followed by a prequel, Bumblebee, in 2018.
The film explores themes of england, chosen one,
based on toy, knight, giant robot.
The tone is thought_provoking.